Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ joeyexp-9ab3171aa (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Acting
Entrepreneurship
Film Actor

Joe Rogan

Stand up comic/mixed martial arts fanatic/psychedelic adventurer Host of The Joe Rogan Experience

United States

Summary

Rogan hosted short-lived CBS show Game Show in My Head that aired for eight episodes in January 2009 and produced by Ashton Kutcher. The show involved contestants who try to convince people to perform or take part in increasingly bizarre situations for money. He agreed to host the show as the idea intrigued him, calling it "a completely mindless form of entertainment"

In December 2009, Rogan launched a free podcast with his friend and fellow comedian Brian Redban. The first episode was recorded on December 24 and was initially a live weekly broadcast on Ustream,[57] with Rogan and Redban "sitting in front of laptops bullshitting".[14] By August 2010, the podcast was named The Joe Rogan Experience and entered the list of Top 100 podcasts on iTunes,[58] and in 2011, was picked up by SiriusXM Satellite Radio. [14] The podcast features an array of guests who discuss current events, political views, philosophy, comedy, hobbies and numerous other topics.[59] In January 2015, the podcast was downloaded over 11 million times.[60] By October that year, the podcast was downloaded 16 million times each month, making it one of the most popular free podcasts.

In 2010, Rogan accused comedian Dane Cook of joke thievery.

In 2011, Rogan resumed his role as Fear Factor host for its seventh and final season, until 2012.Rogan took the job as he "would hate to see somebody else do it.

In 2011, Rogan played his first major character in a movie in Zookeeper.[62] He was also working on a book that he tentatively titled Irresponsible Advice from a Man with No Credibility, based on his blog entries on his website.[14] He played himself in Here Comes the Boom, another action-comedy starring Kevin James released in 2012.

In December 2012, Rogan released his sixth comedy special Live from the Tabernacle exclusively as a download on his website for \$5. He was inspired to release it that way after Louis C.K. did the same thing.

Experience

The Joe Rogan Experience/Game show in my head Host/Producer 2006 - 2009 (3 years)

Rogan began a career in comedy in August 1988 in the Boston area. After relocating to Los Angeles in 1994, Rogan signed an exclusive developmental deal with Disney and appeared as an actor on several television shows including Hardball and NewsRadio. In 1997, he started working for the Ultimate Fighting Championship (UFC) as an interviewer and color commentator. Rogan released his first comedy special in 2000. In 2001, Rogan put his comedy career on hold after becoming the host of Fear Factor and would resume his stand-up career shortly after the show's end in 2006. In 2009, Rogan launched his podcast The Joe Rogan Experience

Stand-up Comedy Stand-up Comedian 2000 - 2006 (6 years)

Ultimate Fighting Championship Interviewer and Color Commentator 1997 - 2000 (3 years)

Hardball and NewsRadio Actor 1994 - 1997 (3 years)

MIXED MARTIAL ARTS FOR REFORM AND PROGRESSION (MMARAP) CIC Fighter 1990 - 1993 (3 years)

Education

Newton South High School

University of Massachusetts Boston